{
    "id": "cb495b432ddc4f34aa46fd2a7c8966a5",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. the pictures on the wall.",
            "description": "Hung is the past tense of hang when it means be suspended from above. ",
            "answers": [
                "hanged",
                "hang",
                "hung"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cbe750cf49bb4039a38cc891a337c0fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was ………………….. for murder.",
            "description": "When hang means to kill someone by hanging, its past tense is hanged. ",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hanged",
                "hang"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc7505685a454789ab78be443a73075f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………. him a moment ago.",
            "description": "The present perfect is not used with the time expression ago. ",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df7c0449b9a944cba105d97f1e4d798d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. in",
            "description": "The present perfect is not used with past time expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "has graduated",
                "graduated",
                "had graduated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87e66ed5779d487380e9907d3db1c441"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. ill for about a month.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "had been",
                "has been",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64d23263570446fb8983d0eb639d9b69"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his phone shortly after he ………………………… it.",
            "description": "The simple or the past perfect is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "had bought",
                "has bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2db8a03e3c424162ac87417b387f0354"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. you for a long time.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "did not see",
                "have not seen",
                "had not seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9bba1f5c56c14fc9b8f0288e926fabed"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… him to go.",
            "description": "Before a personal object, use tell.",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "spoke"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "556ee234255a4a9f83cbb29f542e89d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of the messengers ……………………….. returned.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after either and neither.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b47c21a38eee4a00ba7ea33f2a6a39aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The quality of the apples ………………………… not good.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun quality.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "127674360b40438c950625f011010b82"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my sisters ………………………. abroad.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun one. ",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "521c2db627884db8b4f9bc9247edb93a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother cat with her kittens …………………………. hiding under the bed.",
            "description": "When we connect two subjects with 'with', the verb agrees with the first subject in number. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7da949a1948849ff9da73606883ac1e6"
        }
    ]
}